jamstec.go.jp 2008-12-18

# Basic Policy on the Protection of Personal Information < About JAMSTEC < JAMSTEC

## 

Japan Agency for Marine-Earth Science and Technology (JAMSTEC) will promote various types of collaboration with many countries to conduct global scale research, while actively engaging in activities to disseminate research results and contribute to society. Based on the recognition of the importance of protecting personal information obtained through its activities, JAMSTEC is committed to ensuring that all employees observe the “Law Concerning the Protection of Personal Information Held by Independent Administrative Institutions” and the “Enforcement Ordinance for the Law Concerning the Protection of Personal Information Held by Independent Administrative Institutions”, as well as various regulations established by JAMSTEC. In addition, JAMSTEC has set out the following Basic Policy on the Protection of Personal Information under which JAMSTEC strictly manages personal information.

  1. Acquisition and Use of Personal Information 

JAMSTEC will clearly indicate the purposes of use when acquiring personal information and will not use it for any other purpose.

  2. Security Measures 

JAMSTEC will ensure appropriate safeguarding of personal information by taking security measures to prevent loss, leakage or alteration.

  3. Provision of Personal Information 

JAMSTEC will not provide personal information to third parties for any purpose other than the specified purposes of use, unless required by “laws and regulations”.

  4. Disclosure, Correction and Suspension of Use of Personal Information 

JAMSTEC will promptly respond to a request or complaint concerning disclosure, correction or suspension of use of Personal Information it has obtained, by the person who is the subject of personal information.

  5. Establishment and Amendment of Rules concerning Protection of Personal Information 

JAMSTEC will review the Basic Policy on the Protection of Personal Information and other rules it has established from time to time as necessary.

**Major Purposes of Use**

  * To communicate answers, replies and confirmations to the users of the service provided by JAMSTEC  
*Application for subscription to e-mail magazines, order for purchasing publications, entry in the events, application for use of DB, images and facilities, application for recruitment, application for sponsored research, application for boarding on vessels (passenger list), request for information disclosure/disclosure on personal information protection, etc.
  * To send letters of invitation to various events of JAMSTEC
  * To publish the results of research conducted by JAMSTEC
  * For security control on the premises and vessel security control
  * For smooth and fair operation of JAMSTEC’s activities  
*To make request for speech, appoint committee members, send greeting letters, etc.
